{
    "subject": "resource/Jean_Dieudonn\u00e9",
    "predicate": "ontology/doctoralAdvisor",
    "object": "resource/Paul_Montel",
    "human_readable": "Jean Dieudonn\u00e9's doctoral advisor was Paul Montel.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.960693895816803,
            "question": "What was Paul Montel's role in Jean Dieudonn\u00e9's education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9602518081665039,
            "question": "Who was Jean Dieudonn\u00e9's doctoral advisor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9526671767234802,
            "question": "How might Jean Dieudonn\u00e9's work have been influenced by his advisor, Paul Montel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8490234613418579,
            "question": "What field of study is likely related to both Jean Dieudonn\u00e9 and Paul Montel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5092412233352661,
            "question": "Are there any other notable mathematicians who were advised by Paul Montel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4599786102771759,
            "question": "Can you find any biographical information about Paul Montel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4531855583190918,
            "question": "Did Jean Dieudonn\u00e9 go on to become a successful mathematician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3848607540130615,
            "question": "Can you name a famous mathematician who might have been supervised by Paul Montel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2196323424577713,
            "question": "What kind of relationship existed between a doctoral advisor and their student in the past?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.020323308184742928,
            "question": "What are some of the contributions made by mathematicians in this era?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jean Dieudonn\u00e9's doctoral advisor was Paul Montel.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7017_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of relationship existed between a doctoral advisor and their student in the past?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7017_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a famous mathematician who might have been supervised by Paul Montel?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7017_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Jean Dieudonn\u00e9 go on to become a successful mathematician?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7017_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7017_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7017_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7017_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7017_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7017_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7017_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7017_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7017_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7017_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7017_44.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The text states that \"He received both his bachelor's degree (1927) and his doctorate (1931) from the \u00c9cole Normale.\" Additionally, it mentions that \"His doctoral studied were supervised by Montel\". This implies that Paul Montel was Jean Dieudonn\u00e9's doctoral advisor."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Jean Dieudonn\u00e9's doctoral advisor was Paul Montel.\" Specifically, it mentions that Jean Dieudonn\u00e9 received his doctorate in 1928 under Paul Montel at the University of Nancy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}